Ghost Prison
Liu Qingyan
Liu Qingyan, the eldest miss of the Liu family
Chen Ye
Lord of the Prison
This level of strength
Is it okay?
Yeah.
My lord.
Another woman has arrived outside.
She is making a fuss to see you.
Why is there another one?
Which number is this?
In response to my lord,
This is already the 14th one.
This can't go on like this.
You let that woman wait a moment.
I'll go over there shortly.
Yes.
You are Chen Ye.
That's right.
I am Liu Qingyan.
Your nominal fiancée.
However, from now on...
You and I have no more connection whatsoever.
You don't need to think about it.
Why are you trying to entangle me?
I have an annual salary of over ten million.
Countless luxury cars and villas.
These are all you have for a lifetime.
You won't be able to earn any of it.
Moreover,
You are still a prisoner.
Prisoner.
Who did you hear that from?
You don't need to care who I heard it from.
You are destined to be unworthy of me.
If you know what's good for you...
Then take out the marriage certificate.
I might be generous.